I Gusti Ayu Ngurah Stita Maharani

Malang, East Java, Indonesia | +6282145287612 | stitamaharani@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/stita-maharani

PROFILE

I am an active student majoring in Computer Science at Bina Nusantara University and have a deep interest in UI/UX design and Front-End. I have academic experience in design principles and web programming skills such as HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, with this experience I have produced a variety of interesting and intuitive academic projects.

EDUCATION

Bina Nusantara University – Malang, Indonesia

Computer Science - GPA 3.85/4.00

Sep 2021 - Present

• The courses that I preferred during my studies are Object-Oriented Programming, Database Technology, Web Programming, Software Engineering, and Research Methodology in Computer Science.

SMAK Santo Yoseph - Denpasar, Indonesia

Majoring in Mathematics and Science

Jul 2018 - 2021

EXPERIENCE

Google Developer Student Clubs – Bina Nusantara University – Malang, Indonesia Core Team Design

Sep 2023 - Present

Responsible for designing event requirements such as Instagram posts and posters.

PANORAMA Journalism Student Association – Bina Nusantara University – Malang, Indonesia

Workshop Secretary

Dec 2022 - Jan 2023

Responsible for preparing proposals and accountability reports for the PANORAMA Digital Magazine Workshop.

PANORAMA Journalism Student Association - Bina Nusantara University - Malang, Indonesia

Reporter

Feb 2021 - Dec 2022

Responsible for creating content and news reports to be posted on PANORAMA's Instagram.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Computer Science Student Association (HIMTI)

Online Tutoring Volunteer

Sep - Oct 2022

Responsible for tutoring students of SMAK Santo Yoseph Denpasar about basic C language programming.

PROJECT

Library System Management Website

Front-End Developer

May - Jul 2023

- Developed the idea to build a library system management website for admin and receptionist. On this website, the
 admin can manage members, books, authors, and genres while the receptionist can manage borrowing and
 returning books. This project is developed using Laravel, React, and Bootstrap.
- Responsible for developing the display of the CRUD process on receptionist dashboard and table including the table of library users, members, borrow status, book, and borrow.

.

Nerd Project

UI Designer Feb - Jun 2023

• Developed a project idea to help users improve their learning effectiveness, containing features such as learning documentation with various learning techniques, statistical timelines, and learning communities. The user interface in this project is developed with Adobe XD.

- Create requirement engineering consisting of BMC, VPC, list of stakeholder, functionality, and non-functionality.
- Create software models, including activity diagrams and user interfaces.
- Calculate the function points used in the project.
- Determine the software configuration management process model used in the project.

Big Data Capabilities for Hospital: A Systematic Literature Review

Author

Feb - Jun 2023

- This paper aims to determine the effectiveness of Big Data Analytics in improving performance in hospitals, the key factors to determine the effectiveness of Big Data, the data sources needed, the utilization of Big Data to improve patient satisfaction, and the challenges that will be faced.
- Contributing to the writing of the paper and finding the necessary data.

Seleas Merchan's

Program Developer

Dec 2022 - Feb 2023

- Project GUI using Microsoft Access and Apache NetBeans for Seleas Merchan's business that is used to manage
 deposit payments and full payments. This GUI program was developed using Microsoft Access and Apache
 NetBeans.
- Responsible for developing GUI programs using JAVA language.

Holiday Plane (Hope)

Database Administrator

Dec 2022 - Feb 2023

- Holiday Plane (HOPE) is a database that can be used for online airplane ticket booking software. This database contains data of customers, payment, reschedule, airport, airline, aircraft type, ticket price, tourist attractions, and culinary. This database was developed with XAMPP, MYSQL, PHPMYADMIN, and SQL language.
- Responsible for creating databases by utilizing CRUD, ALTER, and DROP queries.

HONORS & AWARDS

ICCSCI 2023 - Malang, Indonesia

Author

Aug 2023

Received the Best Paper award of the paper "Big Data Capabilities for Hospital: A Systematic Literature Review".

SKILLS

- **Technical**: Basic in C, Python, ReactJs, and Golang; Intermediate in JAVA, SQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Laravel; Advanced in Figma and Adobe XD.
- **Soft Skills**: Creativity, Collaboration, and Problem-Solving.

ADDITIONAL LINK

Portofolio Link
 GitHub Link
 : https://bit.ly/PORTFOLIOSTITA
 : https://github.com/StitaMaharani21